(l'm)

BEN GADWAH

UX / UI

(designer)

Passionate designer experienced in User Experience, UX Strategy, Visual Design, and Marketing. Incorporating Interaction Design, Information architecture, Content Strategy, Visual Identity, Psychology, and Empathy into work. Able to determine success metrics, identify target demographic, and understand the project's objectives and goals.



CONTACT

- **⋪** bengadwah.me
- bengadwah@gmail.com
- 774-314-0901
- in/bengadwah
- @bengadwah



SKILL SET

User Experience, Visual Design, Interaction Design, Information Architecture, User Flows, Sketching, Prototyping, HTML, CSS, Competitive Analysis, Strategy



TOOLS

Photoshop (8 yrs), Typography (8 yrs), Creative Problem Solving (5 yrs), Illustrator (4 yrs), InDesign (3 yrs), HTML & CSS (3 yrs), Sketch (1 yr), HubSpot (1 yr)



EDUCATION

BA, Graphic Design Assumption College

HubSpot Design Certification HubSpot Academy



EXPERIENCE

Boston Children's Hospital Trust Temp

Beacon Hill Staffing (July 2016 - Present)

Primary Client: Boston Children's Hospital

- Coded emails with HTML / CSS and improved the development of campaign email messages
- Developed A/B tests and surveys for emails and reported data for campaign metrics, including: clickthrough rate, donations, and open count

Previous Clients

Independent Consulting (November 2008 - Present)

Monadnock Bible Conference, JC Music, Assumption College, KIIT Renewable Energy, Energy Venture Management, Intelligen. Energy, Loon Mtn Ministry, Charles River Church, Develop. Energy Solutions, CounterMentors

UX Designer

EthoSolar (May 2015 - January 2016)

Now "EthoEnergy" - an Ontario-wide 360 degree solar solution provider

- ★ Redesigned company website that created a better web experience and increased inbound leads
- Lead a company wide brand adjustment with the design, development, and implementation of print and digital communication materials.
- Skills required and developed: UX Strategy, User Research, Information Architecture, Interaction Design, Visual Design, Content Strategy, Data Analysis, Code & Development

Visual Designer

JC Music (September 2010 - May 2011)

Locally owned music store with rentals, repairs, consignments, lessons, and sales

- Developed company-wide brand guidelines that resulted in a harmonious visual identity
- Developed communication materials which facilitated the increase of sales
- Planned effective marketing strategies for private product labels which outsold competition